Name: kodali Tanuj
NUID : 002675123

Assignment 1B is made of 5 pages.

Index.html (1st page) :

The <nav> tag is used for the navbar tab , and I've used the unordered list which <ul> tag and <li>.

To group everything together under a container, use the <div> tag.
used href to navigate to other tab.

also footer is given by using <footer> tag 

about.html (2nd page) 

navigation bar remains the same .

given some content about us in the middle of the website and have given footeer for it to.




schedule.html (3rd page) : 

The navigation bar is the same.

Here, I've utilized a table.
The <table> tag is made up of <thead>, which contains the <th> tags for the table headers.
Table details are contained in several <tr> and <td> tags.

fourth page: videoclips.html

navigation bar is the same.

Here, I've utilized the , IFRAME tag and GIVEN SRC to it so that it can grab the video from ther and also given height and width.

fifth page  commentary.html

navigation bar remains the same.
used audio controls to attach audio which is downloaded in the folder given height and width.

also attached footer.


