Name: kodali Tanuj
NUID : 002675123
Assignment 1: Building a website using HTML and CSS

Part A:
In this part, I have created a four pages website based on the concept of a coffee shop.
1. Index.html :

Index.html is the main page/home page. I have used the  <nav> tag and then the unordered list <ul> list tag.. I used the <a> and href tags to navigate to the other pages.

Using another <div> tag and <h1>,<p> tag for the small description of the webpage.

2. about.html:

With the continuation of the same navbar which was used before on the index page, in this page I have given a brief description about the coffee. Using <tr> for rows, I used the <a> and href tags to navigate to the other pages.

3. ourcoffees.html:

With the continuation of the same navbar, in this page I have mentioned the menu by using tables and the tags are <table> <tr> <th>.  used the <a> and href tags to navigate to the other pages.

4. ourteas.html
With the continuation of the same navbar, in this page I have mentioned the menu by using tables and the tags are <table> <tr> <th>.  used the <a> and href tags to navigate to the other pages.


5. Contact.html:

With the continuation of the same navbar, in this page I have added the address, mobile number and email id of the coffee shop using <p> tag.  I used the <button> tag for a submit button.

